

PROFILE

Hello Everyone! welcome you all in my official website. To introduce myself, recently I have been studying Bachelor of Information Technology at Phoenix College of Management. I have one year of work experiences as a senior Data Analyst and Manager at one of the reputed E-commerce Website namely Online Saathi. In the field of IT, I have good skills and knowledge of following programs.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+977 9816246451

WEBSITE:

https://kshitiz58.github.io/babik37

EMAIL:

kshitizbabik.37@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Programming Photography Designing Reading Novel

KSHITIJ BISHOKARMA

Student

EDUCATION

Mount Everest School

2010 - 2017

I have completed my secondary level of education from my own birth place namely Chandrapur-3, Rautahat with GPA 3.55(A)

Liverpool Int'l College

2017 - 2019

I have completed my 10+2 level of education choosing major subject 'Biology' from Science faculty in Kathmandu with GPA 2.97(B+).

WORK EXPERIENCE

Softech Solution [File Manager]

2019

I have to handle all the data and file and place it in the systematic order.

Online Saathi [Data Analyst]

2020-2021

I have to analyzed all the website data with comparison to other ecommerce websites. I have to also guide other team member in price fixing in new entry product.

Seshra Innovation [Website Design]

2021-Present

I have done internship for around 6 months in Graphics and Website Design and make myself able to design basic designs.

SKILLS

